Copyright from SI Media
Once Upon A Time ...
There 's one word to describe what 's happening ,
And that word is " Panic "
And of course this comes with unthinkable irrational behaviour ,
The crash of 29 ,
... 1987 Black Monday
Came with tragic suicides and murders .
This collapse is no exception .
Just one hour ago as the market were opening ,
2 partners at Cava Holding were shot
at the troubled company 's headquarters .
Senior partner , Laura Muller , died on site .
An analyst , Albert Bernard , is in critical condition .
Jeffrey Dosage , also Senior partner , was in the office
at the time of the shooting and is now gone missing .
I 'm sorry , we , we got to go , sweetheart .
That 's it .
Isn 't Mommy taking me to school ?
Mommy 's not feeling well .
Hurry . Put on yöur glasses . Come on .
Let 's go .
Daddy , where 're we going ?
I don 't know .
Fuck .
yöu 're driving too fast .
- Daddy , yöu 're driving too ... - Shut up !
Sorry , excuse me .
- Hey , buddy , yöu want to get behind the tape ? - I 'm family . I 'm Lucas Desange .
yöu called me . Someone called me . Detective or something ?
- yöu live here ? - No , my brother lives here .
What 's going on ? Where is Jeff ?
Are the girls okay ? Where are the girls ?
Sir , just hang on , all right ? Just wait here .
Jesus Christ .
Jeffrey Dosage apparently shot 2 of his partners to death
... before going on to murder his estranged wife .
And kidnapped his two daughters , age three and one .
It 's okay . It 's okay . Come on .
Daddy , are we there yet ?
My glasses are broken .
What is it ?
It 's okay .
Helvetia
- It 's all right , come here . - There 's someone inside .
Now !
Come on , come on ..
Daddy , there 's a woman outside .
She 's not touching the floor .
Why are yöu crying ?
Because I 'm sad , honey .
Why are yöu sad ?
yöu know ,
Mom and Dad , they
tried real hard .
But sometimes they messed things up .
yöu know Daddy loves yöu , right ?
I can 't see .
What 's that ?
Look honey , there ..
Daddy ?
Look , Lilly . A cherry .
Five Years Later .
Burnsie , where are yöu guys , then ?
Well ...
We 're going to to have a another look around sector 1-7-12-33 .
- That 's the mountain road , right ? - Uhuh .
Gas station ,
Road to the Paulson Pass ..
- This is good . - Oh , God . I hate to do this .
Do what ?
The last payment didn 't clear .
Well , uh ... I 'll check on that .
Don 't worry about that . Things go down .
All right . I 'll work on that and get back to yöu .
" Not Pregnant "
Thank yöu , good bye .
Thank yöu , God . Sweet !
- That was Burnside on the phone ? - Yup .
What is his next move ?
Is he going to search sector lousy alpha ?
Hey , guess who 's not pregnant ?
What is wrong with yöu ?
Last payment didn 't clear .
Is there a problem with the bank , or ...
The money 's gone .
- I pick B. - That is the correct answer .
Look , babe ..
It 's yöur brother. yöu want to spend all yöur money , and find them ,
It 's okay with me . It 's cheaper than therapy .
- And so am I. - What .. ?
I need to go .
- Burnside ! - What ?
Hey , Burnside !
Jesus Christ !
- yöu 're going to call him ? - Just give me a minute .
But we should call , we said we 'd call .
Ronny ,
Shut up .
Just for one minute .
Here yöu go , Bird . Take a whiff of that .
Hello ?
Ah , yes sir . Yes sir . Yes sir .
It 's cherry pits .
Hey , Burnsie !
Burnsie ,
Can we call him now ?
They found them .
- yöu shitting me . - They found the girls .
Alive .
Dr. Gerald Defuses .
- And yöu must be Annabel . - I must be .
- Lucas . - How are they ?
Well , just let me warn yöu . This won 't be easy .
We 're very fortunate , that Victoria was old enough
to retain much of her vocabulary .
But it 's still too early to determine ...
- ... if this development ... - What about the other one ?
That 's a different story .
Shit .
Oh , yeah .
Hey , Victoria .
Is that yöu , Lilly ? Hey ...
No , no , no . It 's okay . It 's okay .
I 'm not going to hurt yöu .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
I brought something for yöu . For yöur eyes .
When yöu were a little girl . yöu had a pair of these. yöu remember ?
I was going to put ... That 's okay .
Just going to put them here .
It 's okay .
Yeah .
That 's it .
Daddy ?
Oh , no , no , honey .
Honey , no , I 'm not yöur Daddy . I 'm ...
I 'm yöur Daddy 's brother .
Remember Uncle Luke ?
Dad ?
It 's okay .
- Dad ? - It 's okay .
Dr. Gerald Defuses , yöur Honour .
The girls have been in my care at the Institute .
Since they were found 87 days ago .
And how would yöu define their progress ?
Solid , and outstandingly fast .
If I may ?
yöur Honour , Victoria and Lilly Dosage
were found in deplorable conditions .
Isolated , starved .
They feared and distrusted all physical contact .
Their emotional growth was clearly compromised
by their abandonment .
In order to survive such extreme isolation ,
The girls created an imaginary guardian .
A parent figure , to feed them ,
Sing to them , protect them .
They called her : " Mama " .
Victoria and Lilly have a real chance
to have a normal life , though . With the right care ,
Physical emotional development .
And much needed love and affection .
- They 'll get better . - Thank yöu , Dr. Defuses .
Ms. Podolski . Would yöu care to address the Court ?
Good morning , yöur Honour .
Jeffrey Desange murdered my niece .
And abandoned his daughters in the forest .
And now his brother did an extraordinary thing .
Lucas never gave up on his nieces .
But he did it for the girls . Not for himself .
So , if he still has their best interest at heart ,
He must know neither his salary , nor his very small apartment
are suitable for the raising of 2 children .
Let alone , 2 children with a very special needs .
- How many kid did yöu raise , Jean ? - Not as many as yöu , Lucas .
Of cause she wants the girls , Lucas . Stand on her shoes first .
She can 't just sweep in , and take them . They are not hers to take .
- I 'm sure that 's not entirely fair . - I 'll tell yöu , what 's not fair :
It 's not fair is she gets to buy my nieces .
- Is that really such a bad thing ? - What ?
Annabel plays in the band .
yöu draw pictures for a living .
Where do yöu live ? Do yöu have room for children in yöur life ?
I mean , really .
What are yöu saying , Gerald ?
When it comes to the girls ' welfare ..
Family Court judge is pretty much oblige to act on my recommendation .
And right now ,
I 'll be lying if I didn 't say it was a slam dunk for Ms. Podolski .
But the truth is ...
I don 't want them living on the other side of the country anymore than yöu do .
So ...
We can really really help each other out right now .
yöu want the girls , I need continued access to them .
What are we going to do ?
This house , courtesy of the Institute , is used for case studies .
Rent-free .
yöu move to the house , yöu get the girls .
This is a joke , right ?
Mr. Desange , is yöur brother still alive ?
Oh , son of a bitch .
- Look , Jean .. - No .
I just want to see them . That 's all .
yöu 'll see them . I mean , yöu 've got visitation , right ? We respect that .
Right now , we need a little space .
Just work on this thing for a while . Find their feet .
- Okay ? - Excuse me .
October the 26th .
Although she seems collaborative ,
And is quickly recovering her language skills .
Victoria maybe repressing the memory
of her experience in the wilderness .
Okay , Victoria .
Are yöu nice and relax ?
Are yöu feeling sleepy ?
I want yöu to tell me the story again .
Can yöu tell me the story ?
It was long time ago ,
A lady run away from hospital for sad people .
She took her baby .
She jumped into the water .
How could yöu know that story , Victoria ?
Did Mama tell yöu that story ?
- She showed me . - How ?
In a dream .
Go on , Victoria .
And yöu can 't tell anyone where yöu are ?
Nope .
That 's just bizarre , dude .
Yeah , well . For the girls .
Few breaths away .
So much deplorable .
All families are the messed up .
Yeah , but this one messed up , and it ends it .
I don 't even have the chance to screw them up . They came that way .
- Leave him . - I can 't .
yöu don 't sign up for this , babe .
I can 't do that to him .
Mrs. Sensitivity ,
yöu are in a rock band .
I was in a rock band , yeah .
Hey , girls .
Hey .
Come here .
Mama .
No , don 't call me that . I 'm not yöur Mom .
I 'm Annabel. yöu can call me that .
Or Annie , or whatever yöu like .
We could ... We could work it out together , right ?
Mama .
Handsome ?
CLIFTON FORGE PUBLIC RECORDS .
There are no police reports between 2008 and 2012
that match the patient 's story .
And Doctor , there are no psychiatric hospitals
anywhere near Clifton Forge .
Where were the closest one would be ?
Falls Church , 200 miles from here .
Now this log book , contains records from St. Kerch 's asylum .
Abided to Salt Lake . That 's 5 miles north from here .
But yöu told me that there are no mental hospitals in the area .
There aren 't . St. Kerch is shut down in 1878 .
Page 31 . Patient Edith Brennan .
- Annabel ? - Yup ?
- Handsome is outside . - Try to put him there .
But he 's crying .
Awesome .
There 's no way these kids are ready for this .
I know it 's tough . It 'll get better . I promise .
I don 't know if I can do this , Luc .
I love yöu , girl .
- Someone 's here ! - What ?
Victoria , Lilly ?
- No one 's here . - Someone 's here . I saw them .
- Wow , wow , honey , honey . - I saw them .
Give me the hammer .
I 'll check downstairs . yöu look after the girls .
Lucas ?
Oh my God .
- Lucas ? - Hi , it 's Vince with Slap Chop .
Chop , chop . Chop , cop .
I 'm really sorry , Annabel .
But they told me he responded well to the tests .
And it 's uh , very likely this coma is temporary .
What happens now ?
I 'm afraid I don 't follow .
- Those girls now without Lucas ... - No .
Annabel , the girls need yöu . They need security ,
Protectability .
But I 'm not prepared for this .
- I can 't do this alone . This is not my job to do . - Just ...
Just follow , if yöu not , yöu 'll lose custody .
And Lucas will be lucky if he sees his nieces every second at Thanksgiving .
Well , I checked out . All the doors and windows are locked .
No evidence of intruder . Nothing 's stolen . So ...
So , I imagined it then , yeah ?
- All right , thank yöu , bud . - Mom ...
Richmond 's finest !
Okay , guys . Just yöu and me for a while .
I don 't know how are yöu feeling about that .
But we got no choice .
How they 've been affected by all of this ?
They are talking to the walls .
What did they say ?
Mama .
What 's this ?
They made that .
They found a doll in the cabin , Victoria .
Who made the doll ?
Mama .
The doll 's called Mama ?
Or Mama made the doll ?
- Mama made the doll . - And who is Mama ?
Are yöu Mama , Victoria ?
This is Dr. Gerald Dreyfuss . Please leave a message .
Dr. Defuses , this is Louise
from Clifton Forge Public Records .
I found something that yöu would want to see .
yöu guys okay ?
What 's so funny ?
Good night .
No !
Whatever .
Nice butt , Bruce .
Victoria ..
Come . Mama .
yöu guys know what time it is ?
I guess yöu wouldn 't . It 's late . It 's really really late .
Don 't .
Don 't what ?
Don 't close the closet .
Why not ? What 's in the closet ?
Nothing .
Okay .
It 's been an along day . So yöu guys should get some sleep . Go to bed .
yöu want me to leave the door open ?
Good night .
Just tell me about it .
I think someone 's coming to visit them .
- Who ? - I don 't know .
- And yöu believe that ? - I heard her .
She was .. singing to them , like a lullaby , or something .
yöu heard her ?
- Definitely a her ? - Yeah .
Sound like this ?
Yeah , but it was , it was different .
Her voice was deeper .
Victoria is showing signs .
A dissociative personality disorder .
I think she could taking on the role of Mama .
Literally , becoming her .
It 's treatable . With time and patience .
Am I safe ?
What ? Look , she 's 8 years old .
Give me a break .
I found second entry under the name of that woman .
Edith Brennan ?
Not Edith Brennan .
Welcome to isle 17 , Doctor .
Every archive has one .
Lost and found of things people don 't want to find .
Twenty years ago , when they moved to Clifton Forge cemetery .
Some of the oldest , smallest remains ,
were not claimed by the relatives .
They were sent here to be filed .
I 'm not a religious person , but I do believe ,
there 's a place for human remains .
And that 's not on the shelf in a Government building .
Do yöu believe in ghosts ?
I can 't say that I do .
When a corpse is left out .
The elements withered . Desiccated ..
Twisting it into a distorted figure that 's barely recognizable as a human being .
A ghost is an emotion went out of shape .
Condemned to repeat itself , time and time again .
Until it rights the wrong that was done .
What 's this ?
The wrong .
Jeff ?
Save my girls .
Go to the cabin .
- What happen ? - Hold him still .
- Lorazepam . 4 milligrams . - 4 milligrams of lorazepam .
Skopolamin .
- Fever ? - No fever , doctor .
Can yöu hear me ?
Relax Mr. Desange .
yöu kicked me out of the bed . Checked on the girls . That as much as I remember .
- For I know that yöu took me . - I would 've managed the job .
Oh , yöu drew me a picture .
It 's a raccoon .
Thank yöu .
I do something for yöu guys too .
There yöu go .
- yöu like it ? - Yeah .
It 's cute .
So , how was it ? Was it a tunnel ? With the light at the end ?
Oh yeah , that was good . Also I stepped into the light .
So , how was it been ? How is the single Mom ?
- That 's great . - Yeah ?
- They 're terrible . They hate me . - They don 't hate yöu .
They hate me .
So easy for yöu to say . yöu 're like the cool uncle .
I am the cool uncle .
What ? What is it , Anny ?
Just get well soon , so yöu can come home , and clean their mess , please ?
yöu sure about this ?
Yeah .
yöu okay ?
What are yöu doing in here ?
Here , I 'll help .
What is it ?
I don 't want yöu to get hurt .
What do yöu mean ?
I 'm fine . Nothing bad is going to happened .
- yöu can 't do that . - Why ?
She gets jealous .
Hey , wait !
What 's wrong with yöu ?
Hello .
Hey , Jean . How can I help ?
It 's my day .
Are yöu sure . I thought that was Thursday .
It is Thursday .
Sorry about the mess .
Children make mess . It 's how it works .
- How are they ? - Adorsey. yöu want coffee ?
Thank yöu .
Oh my God .
What is this ?
I know , they 're wild sometimes .
It 's not an excuse .
Hey , now . They 're bruises . Kids get bruise .
- This bruise ? - It 's not like that .
- Let me have them . - Sorry ?
Just for a few days .
yöu can umm .. I don 't know . Play with yöur band ,
Have a drink with yöur friends .
Jean , I think it 's great .
But the girls have relationship with their own . I really really do .
But right now , I need yöu to get out of my house . Before I kick yöur ass .
I 'll see yöu both very soon , okay ?
Hey !
- Do yöu 've been coming around here ? - I beg yöur pardon ?
Do yöu 've been coming at the house , playing with girls ?
Of cause not ! Why ?
Doesn 't matter .
Richmond ?
Social Services .
Who should I speak to if I believe
my nieces are being abused ?
Well , what kind of evidence do I need exactly ?
- How the hell did yöu forget ? - Are yöu kidding me ?
yöu know she wants to take the girls from us .
I 'm exhausted , I 'm sorry . I forgot today is her day .
Jesus Christ , Anny . It 's one visit . It 's not much to remember .
Anny , listen . They 're just kids . All yöu got to do is ...
What ? Chill out ? Take it easy ?
yöu know I can 't do this . This is not my job .
- This is yöur job . - I 'm out of here in a day ,
- Just hold it together until then . - All right , fine , yeah . We 'll see what happens then .
I 'll take care of them . Those girls are the most important thing in the world to me .
- Awesome . - Anny , yöu ..
Okay , Victoria .
Are yöu nice and relax ?
Are yöu feeling sleepy ?
I 'd like yöu to tell me about Mama .
Did she live in that house with yöu ?
The house by the lake ?
Where did she live ?
In the walls .
Where is she now ?
I don 't know .
I think yöu know .
I think yöu know where she is .
Where is she , Victoria ?
Is she here , in this house ?
Did she come with yöu ?
Open yöur eyes , Victoria .
Look at this photograph .
Is this Mama ?
- Is this Mama , Victoria ? - Go away !
- Tell me about her . - No !
Yes !
What 's going on ?
Nothing . Nothing 's going on .
- Gerald , what happened ? - I have to go .
I 'll call yöu .
November third .
The seventh session was more than revealing .
I think I have found the door , a passage ,
that connects Helvetia into this house ..
There is no rational explanation that supports this theory .
But it is only the ability to embrace the different reality ,
that makes science expand beyond the limits of what we know .
However , extraordinary claims require extraordinary proof .
CLIFTON FORGE - 9 .
I 'm never this close than ever , to the real subject to my research .
I will come back from Clifton Forge , with an answer .
No !
Make her stop !
What 's wrong ?
What 's under the bed ?
Victoria ?
Victoria . Come . Mama .
Victoria .
Come . Mama .
Victoria stay .
Mama ?
Where , Mama ?
I know yöur name .
I know what yöu want .
Lilly ?
Lilly , are yöu okay ?
How did yöu get down here ?
yöu shitting me . Are yöu shitting me ?
Come , yöu crazy .
Okay .
Stop !
Stop it !
Stop .
It 's okay . Come on .
Tenanglah .
Okay , come here .
What ?
yöu like that ?
Okay .
Okay . Door 's good , window 's bad .
So , if yöu want to go outside , what do we do ?
- We use the stairs ? - Right .
Lilly ?
We took stairs ?
Yeah , that 's excellent .
Okay . Let 's go get breakfast .
Oh , God !
Lilly , yöu scared the crap out of me .
Annabel , breakfast is ready !
I 'll be right down !
Annabel !
Lilly 's hungry !
Annabel ?
Yeah .
Victoria. yöu and Dr. Dreyfuss , yöu guys talk some .
I mean , yöu guys talked a lot , right ?
Victoria , Dr. Dreyfuss and I , we talked some too .
We talked about Mama .
yöu and Dr. Defuses. yöu ...
yöu guys talked about Mama too , right ?
Who is Mama , Victoria ?
This is Dr. Gerald Defuses . Please leave a message .
Hey , it 's Annabel . I need to talk to yöu .
So , please call me whenever yöu get this .
Okay , thanks . Bye .
Hypno session 1-5 on tape : Unresposive .
Session 6 on tape : Responsive .
Yes , I talked to him , sir . Two and a half hours ago .
I 'm sure yöu are .
I just don 't understand .
I am afraid that something bad may have happened to the doctor .
yöu okay ?
Sit !
Come on . Get yöur clothes .
Wilson Pass .
Richmond . I need a number for enterprise that rent a car .
Yeah .
CLIFTON FORGE - 9 .
Mama - by Dr. Gerald Dreyfuss .
Tahun 1887 , horror came to Clifton Forge .
What was found at Helvecia was a mystery .
Havebeen someone looking over them ?
Hypnotherapy Session 6 .
I want yöu to tell me the story again .
Can yöu tell me the story ?
It was a long time ago ,
A lady run away from the hospital for sad people .
She took her baby .
She jumped into the water .
How could yöu know the story , Victoria ?
Did Mama tell yöu that story ?
- She showed me . - How ?
- In a dream - Go on .
She fell into the water .
But the baby didn 't .
Why ?
I don 't know .
What could 've happened to the baby , Victoria ?
Mama didn 't show yöu ?
She doesn 't know what happened to her baby .
She went walking in the woods . Looking for it .
She searched for a very long time .
And then ?
Then she found us .
Why are yöu crying , Victoria ?
Because she 's sad .
Disenterrement Request
Is she sad , or are yöu sad , Victoria ?
Where is Mama ?
Is she here with us ?
Can yöu show me Mama ?
She won 't come here .
Why not ?
Because she knows through watching .
This isn 't Annabel . Leave yöur message after the beep .
Fuck yöu . Beep ...
Annabel ?
Hey , Victoria .
Are yöu , okay ?
Yeah , I 'm fine .
Good night , Annabel .
I love yöu .
No .
Lilly !
Don 't look at her !
She 's mad .
Go up ! Lilly !
Lilly !
Lily ! Open the door !
- Victoria , what 's going on ? Are yöu okay ? - Annabel .
It 's Lilly !
Lilly ?
Are yöu okay ?
Mama , stop it !
yöu promise !
Leave her alone !
Annabel ?
Annabel !
Aunt Jean ?
Are yöu okay ?
Lilly ?
Victoria ?
Hey , this is Lucas . Leave a message .
Lucas , she has the girls . I 'm heading to Clifton Forge .
Luc !
I got yöur message .
What the hell are yöu doing here ?
- Where are the girls ? - She took them .
- What ? - I saw her . She 's real .
- What the hell 's happening ? - She 's going to kill them .
We got to get to the cabin . She was here with them the whole time .
Dr. Defuses knew it .
Oh , God .
Jean ?
They 're on the cliff !
Victoria ! Lilly !
No !
- No ! No ! - Mama !
Lilly ! Lilly !
No !
Mama !
Edith !
- Mama ! - No !
Lilly ?
No .
Mama , no , Mama !
Mama !
Stay here .
Bye , Annabel .
Sleep , Annabel !
Victoria , Lilly .
No ...
Sleep , Annabel , sleep !
Sleep !
Good bye , Mama ..
I love yöu .
Victoria , come .
Victoria stay .
Come . Lilly . Mama . Victoria .
No . Lilly . Mama .
Lilly !
- Lilly ! - Victoria , no .
- No . - Lilly !
- Lilly ! - No ...
Oh God , bring her back ...
Please ...
Lilly !
No !
Lilly .
Lilly ?
" Hope You 've Liked Enjoyed The Movie "
Copyright from SI Media